A Guide to the University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Budget Reports, 1950-1957
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Budget Reports 1950-1957
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-16/1/5.771
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Division of Continuing Education, 1977 July 11.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of budget reports of the Division of Continuing Education.
Arrangement
The reports are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Annual Reports- Departmental, 1949-1950 (Folder 1)
- Annual Report Appendix- Community Services, 1949-1950 (Folder 1)
- Budget Adopted, 1949-1951, 2 folders. (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1950-1951 (Folder 1)
- Monthly Financial Reports, 1950-1951 (Folder 1)
- Budget Requests, 1950-1952 (Folder 1)
- Annual Department Reports, 1950-1957 (Folder 1)
- Data, 1951 (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1951-1952 (Folder 1)
- Departmental Budgets, 1951-1962 (Folder 1)
- Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Folder 1)
- Monthly Financial Reports, 1951-1952 (Folder 1)
- Proposed Budget, 1951-1952 (Folder 1)
- Annual Reports, 1952-1953 (Folder 2)
- Budget- Extension, 1952-1953 (Folder 2)
- Extension Centers' Annual Reports, 1952-1953 (Folder 2)
- Monthly Financial Reports, 1952-1953 (Folder 2)
- Budget- Extension, 1954-1955 (Folder 2)
- Monthly Financial Reports, 1954-1955 (Folder 2)